Next, we will introduce a
sound transition with a division line.
We still compare the style and the original shape.
Look at the left side of our screen.
After comparing, we will find that the A sound is gone.
The Xionglong sound is also gone.
There is one more division in the shoulder.
It's good to draw the division line here.
These two sounds are gone,
but there are some folds on the division line.
This means that the A sound and the Xionglong sound
are transferred to the division line.
They are transferred to the shoulder.
Of course, the B sound is also gone.
It needs to be eliminated.
In this case, there is a division line.
This division line has not passed through any sound.
So in this case,
if there is a division line,
draw the division line first.
Draw an internal line.
You can also draw the internal line of the shoulder line.
If you want to draw the internal line of the shoulder line,
click on the shoulder line,
then click on the right mouse button,
then click on the shoulder line,
add an internal line shoulder line,
and you can decide the size based on the style.
Let's say we set it to 45,
or 40.
It's all right.
It's based on the style.
It's drawn like this.
This way, it's the most balanced.
Let's delete it before we choose.
We will choose a balanced one.
If there is a division in this case,
and he doesn't pass through,
let's cut it off first.
Let's say this is a piece of material.
Take this piece out.
Then,
After taking it out, we need to remove these two, first we need to remove the B-throat and then transfer the A-throat to the shoulder line.
After opening it, there will be a lot of wrinkles on this side.
Next, we still remove the B-throat according to the previous operation.
In fact, you can also do a B-throat removal first and a B-throat non-removal first.
Removal is more suitable for this kind of joint type with the waistline broken.
If these two lines are not equal, there will be no rotation.
The function is like this.
Let's see 118.3.
Let's change this line to 118.3.
Then the direction of the B-point cannot be moved.
The direction is directed to the outside.
Adjust to the end.
118.3
Next, we choose these two edges.
Press the mouse button on the right to select these two edges.
Rotate the shoulder line.
We press the shoulder line to the starting point.
The starting point must be the division line.
Then the middle point is the B-point.
Rotate the shoulder line as small as possible.
Select the left button, press the small button, and move the mouse.
Then the shoulder line is also moved.
Then press the left button again.
This time, the shape of the throat is not the shape of the throat.
It is the shape of the fold.
So we don't determine the shape of the throat.
We just move the shoulder line to the top.
After moving the shoulder line,
we do the following.
Remove the lower throat.
Then we press the Shift key to select the two edges of the A-throat.
Rotate the throat.
The starting point of the throat is still the division line.
Drag it to the B-point.
Then we still have a small hole.
Push the B-point directly to the top.
In this way, the shoulder line and the shoulder line are all transferred to the division line.
But if the current division line is set to a fold,
then this angle is OK.
But now the style is a broken fold.
If it is a broken fold, we need to adjust it to be smooth.
We can delete it all.
After deleting it,
we use the editor to adjust it to be smooth.
After adjusting it,
we delete this part.
The front center line.
We pull it out.
We cut it off.
After cutting it off,
we delete this part.
There is no need to keep it.
Delete it.
In the process of drawing,
we can delete all the broken lines.
After deleting it,
we select the left key.
Select the front center line.
Click the right key.
Select the opposite.
Open the border line.
In this way,
it opens.
After opening,
we seal it.
Select the line and seal.
We seal the side seam.
Because the voice is transferred,
it will default to your previous voice.
The edge of the voice is to be sealed.
We delete the sealed line.
We can also turn this point into a free-line point.
Try to reduce the line as much as possible.
Except for some very important points.
Try to reduce the point as much as possible.
Then we also make the waist line smooth.
After making it smooth,
select these points in the frame.
Then we turn it into a free-line point.
Next,
we divide the border line.
The border line of the shoulder.
Press the shift line.
The front line is also divided.
Yes, after dividing it,
now we round off the whole piece.
Now we round off the whole piece.
The one in 3D is better, right?
Yes, after dividing it,
the front line is also divided.
The front line is also divided.
Now we check if the border line is wrong.
If there is no fault,
we can simulate it.
If no fault,
then we can simulate it.
Because we round off.
So we need to turn it into a井
Ok,
What's our next step?
In particular, when a long-line and a short-line are interlocked,
the short-line is easy to be pulled out of shape.
To avoid this,
we can turn on the elasticity of the short-line of the border line above,
and adjust its proportion to 100%.
At this time, it is not easy to be pulled out of shape.
Since we do not have a high-quality product,
if we want a more natural and smooth effect,
especially if we do not have a lot of voice twists,
then we need to improve the quality.
Okay, we can see that it is very similar to the style in the picture.
Let's look at the side bulge.
The bulge on the side is also very similar to the round shape,
but the shape is different.
The position of the throat has turned into the shoulder,
and the shape has become a fold from the throat.
From this position, we can shape the base.
Thank you very much.